《迷失》前情提要
Previously on "lost"...
Jack要去引爆一颗氢弹
Jack is on his way to blow up a hydrogen bomb.
我们得阻止他
We have to stop him.
Jack  我们一定要在事情发生的那一刻赶到
Jack, we need to be there at the moment of the incident.
怎么停下了
Why the hell are we stopping?
看
That's why.
Kate  怎么了
What's going on, kate?
医生 我们需要谈谈
Doc, we gotta talk.
想谈话  那么就上车  我们没时间
You wanna talk? Then get in the van. We don't
-我不会上车的
-Have time  -I ain't get in the van.
我只需要五分钟就够了
I need five minutes, that's all.
我只说我想说的
I'll say what I gotta say,
然后随便你怎么样都行
And then you can do whatever the hell you want to.
但你要听我说  因为你欠我的  Jack
But you're gonna listen. You owe me that much, Jack.
五分钟
Five minutes.
Shephard医生  你还好吗
Dr. Shephard? You all right?
硬膜囊  我切到了
The dural sac...i cut it.
-帮我吸管  -镇定  没事
-Give me some suction.  -Calm down. It's all right.
-流得到处都是  我不能  -看着我
-The fluid's leaking everywhere. I can't  -Look at me.
-帮我吸管  -是  医生
-Give me some suction.  -Yes, doctor.
Jack  看着我
Jack... look at me.
-数到五  -你在说什么
-Count to five.  -What are you talking about?
我是说你要缝上这个切口
I'm talking about you stitching up the sac
别让这个女孩残废下半辈子
So this girl isn't paralyzed for the rest of her life.
而唯一的方法就是不要害怕
And the only way you're gonna do that is not to be afraid.
所以闭上眼睛  数到五
So close your eyes, count to five,
然后把她治好  Jack
And then fix her, Jack.
否则就要换我上阵了
Or i'll have to fix her for you.
一
One...
二
Two...
三
Three...
四
Four...
五
Five.
缝线
Sutures.
Hey  孩子  那个女孩正在康复中
Hey, kiddo. Girl's in recovery.
她下半身对刺激有反应
She's responsive to stimulus below the waist,
所以  不会瘫痪
So... no paralysis.
有什么事吗  Jack
Something wrong, Jack?
你真让我丢脸
You embarrassed me.
是吗
Did i?
让医院所有人
It's bad enough
都认为我之所以得到这个实习机会
That everybody in this hospital thinks
是因为你是我的父亲
The only reason I got this residency
这已经够糟了  但是你却还-
Is because you're my father. But then you...
你居然在我第一次大型手术中间叫暂停
You put me in a time-out during my first major procedure,
而且还当着所有医护人员的面
In front of my entire team.
爸  我知道你不相信我
Dad, I know you don't believe in me,
但我需要他们相信
But I need them to.
你确定我就是那个
Are you sure I'm the one
不信任你的人吗  Jack
Who doesn't believe in you, Jack?
有一个是你的吗
One of these yours?
机器卡住了
Machine got stuck.
我看只是缺乏去摇一下它
I guess it just needed a little push.
坐下歇歇吧  医生
Take a load off, doc.
不必了  谢谢
No, thanks.
坐下  Jack
Sit down, Jack.
我父母在我八岁时就去世了
My folks died when I was 8 years old.
我跟你说过吗
I ever tell you that?
我父亲的东西都被骗子骗走了
Con man took my dad for everything he had.
他无法控制自己  所以
He didn't handle it too well, so...
他开枪打死了我母亲  然后自杀
He shot my mom, then he blew his own head off.
事情发生的时候我就躲在床下
I was hiding under the bed when it happened.
我听到了一切
I heard the whole thing.
-真抱歉  -是啊
-I'm sorry.  -Yeah.
那是一年前的事了
That was a year ago.
什么
What?
现在是1977年七月
Right now it's July 1977,
这说明那是去年的事
Which means that happened last year.
我本可以跳上潜水艇
So I could've hopped on the sub,
回到美国
Gone back to the states,
走进我的家
Walked right in my house
然后阻止我父亲杀人
And stopped my daddy from killing anybody.
你为什么没这么做
Why didn't you?
因为  Jack
Because, Jack...
已经发生的事情不可能挽回
What's done is done.
不一定要那样
It doesn't have to be that way.
你到底在想什么竟然发疯到愿意
What did you screw up so bad the first time around
去引爆一个核武器
You're willing to blow up a damn nuke
-来找第2次机会  -不是这样的
-Just for a second chance?  -That's not what this is about.
那是怎么回事
Then what is it about?
三年前
Three years ago,
Locke告诉我所有这一切事出有因
Locke told me that all this was happening for a reason,
我们命中注定要来到这里
That us being here was our destiny.
我不信命
I don't speak "destiny."
当一个人尽自己所能做某件事的时候
What I do understand is a man does what he does
他一定是为了什么目标
'cause he wants something for himself.
你的目标是什么  Jack
What do you want, Jack?
她曾经和我在一起
I had her.
我们在一起  然后我失去了她
I had her, and I lost her.
Kate
Kate.
那么好吧  医生
Well, damn, doc,
她就在这些树的背后
She's standing right on the other side of those trees.
你想追回她  就去问她啊
You want her back, just go and ask her.
不  已经太晚了
Nah, it's too late for that.
你的五分钟到了
Your five minutes is up.
Jack
Jack...
就算你的方法可行
If what you're doin' even works,
你和Kate还是会分道扬镳
You and kate will be strangers,
而且她会被戴上手铐
And she'll be in damn handcuffs.
如果这是命中注定  我们也只能认命
If it's meant to be, it's meant to be.
那么  我看我说什么
Well, I guess there's nothing I can say
-都改变不了你的主意了  -没错
-That's gonna change your mind.  -No, I guess there's not.
你觉得你算什么
Who the hell do you think you are?!
你以为可以来这里
You think you can come here
然后为所欲为吗
And do whatever the hell you want?
这是我的家
I had a life here!
Sawyer
Sawyer...
你会住手吗
Will you stop?
-你会不会住手  -不会
-Will you stop?!  -No.
James
James!
放开他
Let him go.
他不听  我必须这么做  他不肯住手
He wouldn't listen. i had to. he won't stop!
那是因为他做得对
That's because he's right.
什么
What?!
他说的对  James
He's right, James.
我们是迫不得已
We have to do this.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?!
是你叫我回来阻止他的
You're the one that told me to come back here and stop him!
怎么回事
What happened?!
我改主意了
I changed my mind.
女孩们  爸爸和我有些事情
Girls... your dad and I have something
要告诉你们两个
We need to talk to you both about.
我们又要搬家了吗
Are we moving again?
不是  笨蛋  是他们要离婚了
No, stupid. They're getting a divorce.
-Rachel  -不是吗
- Rachel... - well, aren't you?
-是的  -但是
- Yes. - But...
你们要知道
We need you both to understand
爸爸和我
That your father and I...
我们仍旧相爱
We still love each other.
只是因为两人相爱
Just because two people love each other,
并不意味着他们就要在一起
Doesn't always mean they're supposed to be together.
可你们不是应该在一起的吗
But what if you are supposed to be together?
我们不是的  亲爱的
We're not, honey.
-你们凭什么那么肯定  -我们就是知道
- But how can you know for sure? - We just know.
以后你长大了
And when you're a grown-up,
也会知道的
You'll understand.
我才不想知道呢
I don't wanna understand!
Juliet  等等
Juliet, wait!
我永远都不想知道
I don't wanna understand!
停下  我们得好好谈谈
Stop! We gotta talk about this!
没什么好谈的了  James
There's nothing to talk about, James.
我们要让Jack完成他来这的使命
We have to let Jack do what he came here to do.
或许你应该在我把他赶出丛林前
Well, maybe you should told me you had a change of heart
告诉我你变心了
Before I brought him out in the jungle to kick his ass.
那样做你就舒服了吗
Would that soft you?
-没有  -那好  我很高兴
- No. - well, then I'm glad you finally
你终于能换个方式思考了
Got it out of your systerm.
-嘿  嘿  -别这样
- Hey! hey! - You, don't.
你得告诉我整个的来龙去脉
I need you to tell me where all this is coming from.
我是说  1分钟前  你还在带领大家逃亡
I mean, one minute, you're leading the great sub escape,
而现在你却在指挥炸毁这该死的岛
And now you're on board with blowing up the damn island?
我有权知道你改变主意的原因
I got a right to know why you changed your mind.
我改主意是因为我看见你在看她
I changed my mind when I saw you look at her.
别  别这样
Don't. don't.
我可不管我在看谁
I don't care who I looked at.
我爱的是你
I'm with you.
如果我愿意  你会和我永远在一起
And you would stay with me forever if I let you,
这也是我爱你的原因
And that is why I will always love you.
你不爱我的  我们拥有的只是一段短暂的时光
You don't... what we had, it was just for a little while.
只是因为我们相爱
And just because we love each other,
并不意味着我们就要在一起
It doesn't mean that we're meant to be together.
我是说  或许我们永远不要奢望能在一起
I mean, maybe we were never supposed to be together.
所以如果Jack可以
So if Jack can make it that...
阻止你们从一开始来这里 他就必须做
that none of you ever come here  Then he should.
Juliet  你为什么要这样做
Why you doing this, Juliet?
我...
I...
若我从没遇见过你  那么我就永远不会失去你了
If I never meet you, then I never have to lose you.
Radzinsky
Radzinsky!
现在怎么样了
What is it now?!
高斯指针已经跳出图表范围了
The gauss readings has jumped off the charts.
我来看看
Let me see.
就是它了  我们脚下就有能量袋
This is it! We're on top of the pocket!
如果我们继续钻  直到抵达能量袋
If we keep drilling and hit that pocket,
地狱将会降临
All hell is gonna break loose!
radzinsky  你
radzinsky, are y
-Stuart  快下来  -你想怎么样  Phil
- Stuart, come in! - What do you want, Phil?
那个朝孩子开枪的敌人  他回来了
That hostile that shot the kid? He came back.
你到底在说什么啊
What the hell are you talking about?
就在兵营里  他  他袭击我们
Here at the barracks. He...he attacked us
然后被他的同伙救走了
And then got rescued by some of the other recruits.
他们偷了一辆货车逃跑了
They stole a van and took off.
去了哪里
Took off where?
不知道
I don't know,
Roger说他们其中一人携带有炸弹
But Roger said that one of them had a bomb.
那人知道天鹅站
That hostile knows about the swan!
召集人手  带上枪
Get some men and some guns,
赶快到这边来
And get your asses out here right now!
如果他们朝这边来  我们可要好好准备了
If they're coming here, we're gonna be ready for 'em.
快点
Come on!
Jack  怎么回事
Jack? What happened?
我和Sawyer不欢而散
Yeah, my talk with Sawyer didn't go so good.
很疼吗
Does it hurt?
-还好吧  -那就好
- Ah, it's okay. - Okay.
还记得我们相遇吗  我们第一次到这里时
Do you remember when I sewed you up? when we first got here?
像是很久远的事情了
Seems like a million years ago.
或者是30年后的事情
Or 30 years from now.
Kate  为什么要我承诺永不问起Aaron呢
Kate, why'd you make me promise to never ask about Aaron?
因为我
Because I was...
很生气你叫我又回到这里
So angry with you for making me come back here.
是因为他你才回来的吗
Is he why you came back?
我回来了  他就能和他母亲一起
I came back so he could be where he belongs...
回到他应该在的地方了
With his mother.
如果这样做有用  Claire就不会来到这个岛上
If this works, Claire will never come to the land,
他们就能永远在一起了
And they'll always be together,
就像他们想的那样
Just the way they're meant to be.
可是她当时想不要他
She was gonna give him up for
你不会知道她要做什么的
Well, you don't know what she would do.
不管做什么  都是她自己的选择
And whatever it is, it would be her choice.
如果你还想救Claire  这是唯一的方法
If you wanna save Claire, this is the only way to do it.
我在我一生中从未这么肯定过
Nothing... nothing in my life has ever felt so right.
还有
And...
我希望你能相信我
I just need you to believe that.
继续
Go!
继续钻
Keep going!
继续钻下去
Keep the drill going!
有事要发生了
It's about to happen.
你支持我吗
Are you with me on this?
是的
Yes.
那我们走
Then let's go.
一个皮夹
One wallet.
227美元现金
$227 cash.
一支圆珠笔
One ballpoint pen.
一块水果糖
One fruit roll-up.
在这签个字
Sign here.
你不知道  这是个超级失误
You don't understand. This is a big mistake.
我杀了一群人
I killed a bunch of people.
看到这个了吗
You see this?
这是释放表格  你已经被证明无罪了
This is a discharge form. You've been cleared.
-拿上你的东西走吧  -我说  老兄
- So take your stuff and go. - Look, dude...
有人拿着麻醉枪
There are men with tranquilizer guns
像狩猎一样追捕我
Hunting me down like an animal.
他们会不顾我的意愿把我带走
They wanna bring me somewhere against my will.
外面就有一辆出租车
There's a cab stand right out front.
对不起  我不知道已经有人坐了
Oh. Sorry. I didn't see it was taken, dude.
实际上  我过几条街就下了
Actually, I'm only going a few blocks
我们可以一起
If you wanna share.
进来吧
Come on in.
吃糖吗 樱桃味的
You want some? Cherry.
不要  谢谢
No thanks.
你怎么进去的
So what were you in for?
什么
Excuse me?
监狱
Jail.
我进去的罪名是杀了三个人
I was there 'cause i killed three people.
可我并没有  我想他们搞清楚了
But i didn't really. i guess they figured it out.
你呢
What about you?
我没坐牢
I wasn't in jail.
那你在监狱外面干什么
Well, then what were you doing sitting outside a prison?
还坐在出租车里
In a cab?
Hugo  我是在等你
I was waitin' for you, Hugo.
那你肯定已经死了
Then you must be dead.
我确定我现在活着
I'm definitely not dead.
你想要我做什么
Well, what do you want from me?
我想知道为什么你不回岛上去
I wanna know why you won't go back to the island.
因为我被诅咒了
'cause i'm cursed.
是这样吗
Is that so?
所以飞机才会坠毁  我的朋友才会死
That's why the plane crashed, my friends died...
Libby  Charlie
Libby, Charlie.
现在他们来找我了
Now they visit me,
而我没办法阻止
And i can't make it stop.
如果并不是被诅咒呢
Well, what if you weren't cursed?
要是你是被保佑的呢
What if you were blessed?
你说的保佑是指什么
How do you mean "blessed?"
那你得和你失去的人们谈谈
Well, you get to talk to people you've lost...
这事对于我而言很神奇
Seems like a pretty wonderful thing to me.
我肯定那是很神奇的
Oh, i'm sure it's wonderful,
除了我发疯的那部分
Except for the part where i'm crazy.
Hugo  我有些消息要告诉你
I've got some news for you, Hugo,
你得相信我说的话
And you're just gonna have to take my word on this.
你并没有发疯
You are not crazy.
老兄  你到底是谁
Who are you, dude?
我在路口下车
I'm just up here on the corner.
Ajira航空  316航班  洛杉矶国际机场
Ajira airways flight 316 out of l.a.x.
24小时内起飞
Leaves in 24 hours.
你要做的就是坐上那趟飞机
All you have to do is get on that plane.
Hugo  由你选择
It's your choice, Hugo.
你不必做那些你不愿意做的事
You don't have to do anything you don't want to.
等等  你的吉他
Wait! you forgot your guitar.
这不是我的吉他
It's not my guitar.
一切都会好起来的  待Jack改变未来
Everything'll be fine when Jack changes the future...
或者改变过去
Or the past.
哪个都行
One of those.
我不认为你的朋友能办到
I don't think your bud's gonna make it.
他能行的
He'll make it.
你脸上怎么了
Dude, what happened to your face?
没什么
Nothin'.
我们刚爬上了山脊
We were just up on a ridge
从那里能俯瞰天鹅站
Where we could look down into the swan site.
那里出事了
Something just happened down there.
他们钻到了什么  我该去了
They hit something. it's time for me to go.
都准备好了
It's all set to go.
记住  要当心
Remember, be careful.
它被设定成受到撞击就引爆
It's rigged to explode on impact.
根据Faraday的计划
According to Faraday's plan,
你必须让炸弹
You must get the bomb as close as you can
尽可能靠近磁源
To the source of electromagnetism.
Sayid  计划会成功的
Sayid, this is gonna work.
你会得救的
And it'll save ya.
没什么能救得了我
Nothing can save me.
我们洛杉矶再会
See ya in los angeles.
这是什么  我们怎么停下了
What is it? Why are we stopping?
你会知道的
You'll see.
这只脚挺好看,Richard 但是和Jacob有什么关系
Well, it's a wonderful foot, Richard,but what's it have to do with Jacob?
他住在这里
It's where he lives.
我的天
Oh, my God!
我的天  快报警
Oh, my God! Call 911!
别担心  不会有事的
Don't worry,everything's gonna be all right.
我对你的遭遇感到遗憾
I'm sorry this happened to you.
你确定要这么做吗
Are you sure you need to do this?
如果你再等等  Jacob总会来找你的
If you waited, Jacob would eventually come to you, John.
我等烦了  Richard  他在哪儿呢
I'm tired of waiting. where is he, Richard?
剩下的雕像怎么了
What happened to the rest of the statue?
我不知道  我到这儿时就这样了
I don't know. it was like that when i got here.
你要我相信这话吗
Do you expect me to believe that?
不尽然
Not really.
好了  Ben  我们走了
All right, Ben, let's go.
你来干什么
W-what are you doing?
John要我跟他一起
John wants me to join him.
-你不能带上他  -为什么不能
- You can't bring him in. - Why not?
因为只有我们的领导者才能和Jacob对话
Because only our leader can request an audience with Jacob,
岛上一次只能有一位领导者
And there can only be one leader on the island
John  我
At a time, John. I'm
Richard  你去慢慢制定你的那些规则吧
You just make these rules up as you go along, Richard.
Ben得跟着我  要是出了什么问题
Ben is coming in with me, and if that's a problem,
我相信Jacob和我能解决
I'm sure Jacob and i can work it out.
代我问好
Tell him i said hello.
你能下得了手吧  Ben
Will you be able to do this, Ben?
我知道这不容易
I know it won't be easy,
但情况会改变的  一旦他消失了
But things will change... once he's gone.
我保证
I promise.
能问你件事吗  Lafleur
Can i ask you something, Lafleur?
这里已经没有Lafleur了  说吧  Enos
There ain't no more Lafleur, Enos. go ahead, shoot.
你们有没有想过
Has it occurred to any of you that your buddy's
你的朋友是要去引发那件
Actually gonna cause the thing
他说他想要避免的事
He says he's trying to prevent
也许核武器就是那行动
Perhaps that little nuke is the incident?
所以也许最好我们
So maybe the best thing to do...
什么都不要做
Is nothing?
我很高兴你们都想清楚了
I'm glad you all thought this through.
出什么事了
What's going on?
是Phil
It's Phil.
那是去swan的路
That's the road to the swan.
要是他们见到Jack  他们会杀了他的
If they see Jack, they're gonna kill him.
金发女  你怎么想
What do you think, Blondie?
一起生活  独自死去
Live together, die alone.
-你来得真快  -有没有发现他们的行迹
- Good for you. you got here fast. - Any sign of 'em yet?
还没有  你还有时间在外围设防
No, not yet. you got time to set up a perimeter.
你安排这些人就位
you called these men to reset
你  山后  你  山顶
You, rear ridgeline. you, top ridgeline.
你得带你的人离开这里
we need to be getting your people away from here.
你  上脚手架  马上去
You, top of the scaffolding. go now!
在那儿
There!
抓住他
Get him!
包抄他  把他抓住
Flank him! Get him now!
是谁
Who's this?!
-放下枪  Phil  不然你就死定了  -好  好
- Drop it, Phil, or you're a dead man! - Okay, okay.
让他们把枪放下
Tell 'em to put their guns down.
把枪放下
Drop the guns!
你可以出来了  医生
All right, you can come out now, Doc!
赶紧去做你的事
Hurry up and do your business.
把那该死的东西关了
Turn that damn thing off!
怎么回事
What's the matter?!
关不上了
It won't shut down!
为什么关不上
Why not?!
有东西在往下拽钻头
Something's pulling the drill down.
我们钻到那能量袋了
We hit the pocket!
快点  医生  还等什么呢  扔下去
Hurry up, Doc! what are you waiting for?! drop it!
这看起来不像L.A.X
This don't look like L.A.X
爸
Dad!
Jack!
爸
Dad!
离开这  能多远就多远
Get away from here! get as far away from here as you can!
上车
Get in!
发生什么了  离开这
What the hell's going on?! get out of here!
快
Come on!
快点
Go! go! go!
救命
Help!
Sawyer  救命  Juliet
Sawyer! help! Juliet!
Sawyer
Sawyer!
你以为要去哪  金发美女
Where do you think you're going, blondie?
Kate  帮我把这些链子弄掉
Kate! help me get those chains off!
抓住  你坚持住
Hold on! you hold on!
我  我没办法
I can't. i can't get it off.
-抓住你了  -我
I got you. i can't...
Juliet  不
Juliet! no!
我够不到她  你坚持住
I can't reach her. you hold on!
我抓住你了
I got you.
Sawyer
Sawyer!
别离开我
Don't you leave me.
没关系
It's okay.
别离开我
Don't you leave me!
-我爱你  -别放手
I love you. no, you don't let go!
-我爱你 James  -别放手
I love you, James. don't let go.
-我如此爱你  -不
I love you so much. no!
不  别放手
No, don't let go!
Juliet
Juliet!
不
No!
喝水么
Water?
你有没有酒
Do you have any alcohol?
我也希望我有
No. sure wish i did.
别开枪
Don't shoot.
没关系
It's okay.
没事
It's all right.
你们谁是Ricardus
Which one of you is Ricardus?
是Richard
It's Richard, actually.
雕像阴影下是什么
What lies in the shadow of the statue?
Ille qui nos omnes servabit.
Richard
Richard...
我是Ilana
I'm Ilana.
我有点东西给你看一下
I have something you need to see.
打开
Open it up.
没关系的  让他们开
It...it's okay. it's okay. let them.
你在哪找到他的
Where did you find him?
在飞船的货舱里  我们来这的那艘
In the cargo hold of the plane we came here on...
在棺材里
In a coffin.
我不明白
I don't understand.
如果说这个是Locke
If this is locke...
那个是谁
Who set in there?
你喜欢这个
You like it?
我自己做的
I did it myself.
纫针可费了好多时间
It takes a very long time when you're making the thread,
但是
But, uh...
我看  这是个关键点吧
I suppose that's the point, isn't it?
你好  Jacob
Hello,Jacob.
你找到了关键点了
Well, you found your loophole.
是的
Indeed i did.
你跟不本知道
And you have no idea
我经历过了什么才能 到这
What i've gone through To be here.
你们之前见过么
Have you met before?
礼貌的说
In a manner of speaking.
你该做我叫你去做的事了  Ben
Do what i asked you to, Ben.
Benjamin
Benjamin...
不管他之前和你说了什么
Whatever he's told you,
我希望你了解一件事
I want you to understand one thing.
你有选择
You have a choice.
什么选择
What "choice"?
你可以按他说的做
You can do what he asked,
或者  离开
Or you can go,
离开我们  让我们自己讨论我们的
Leave us to discuss our...
问题
Issues.
哦 这么说  过了这么久
Oh... so now, after all this time,
你们终于不无视我了
You've decided to stop ignoring me.
整整35年  我都住在这个岛上
35 years i lived on this island,
我只听过你的名字
And all i ever heard was your name
一遍一遍
Over and over.
Richard给我带来你的命令
Richard would bring me your instructions...
所有这些页纸
All those slips of paper,
所有这些事情
All those lists...
我从来不怀疑
And i never questioned anything.
全部听指示做
I did as i was told.
但是当我终于有勇气要求要见你的时候
But when i dared to ask to see you myself,
我却被告知  你得等
I was told, "you have to wait.
你得有耐心
You have to be patient."
但是他要见你的时候呢
But when he asked to see you?
他像摩西一样大步走来
He gets marched straight up here as if was moses.
所以  为什么是他
So... why him?
我到底有什么问题
What was it that was so wrong with me?
为什么不是我
What about me?!
你要怎样
What about you?
他们要来了
They're coming.
什么
What?
听不清
I can't hear you.
他们要来了
They're coming.
Juliet
Juliet!
Sawyer  离开那
Sawyer, get off of there!
我们必须现在就走
We have to go right now. we need to go!
离开
Get off.
它要塌了  这东西它
It's going down! this thing is
你必须走  这东西
You have to go. this thing is
随时都会塌的
going to blow at any second
Jack  帮我把他弄走
Jack! help me get him off.
快 混蛋
Come on! You son of a bitch!